so i don't really see people talking about this but meta has already started censoring political
content on instagram and threads so obviously i create content about history and politics and
there's a screenshot from my own settings where the default is to limit political or social topics
that show up on my explore page reels and feed recommendations and once again their big headline
was that this only affects political content but as you can see here it includes social topics what
does that even mean and while politicians are trying and of course failing to convince us that
the tiktok ban is not one big middle finger to free speech you have tiktok's biggest competitor and
alternative quite literally saying that they're going to restrict the use of their platform for
spreading awareness around the issues in our society but until this policy is hopefully done away with
here's how you can change those settings first go to your profile and click these three lines at the
top then scroll down until you see content preferences which will be right here then go to where it says
political content and change it to don't limit but did you know about this and how do you feel about it
should meta change this default setting let me know in the comments and follow for more